{"test_questions": [[{"question": "Using the Relative Polar Coordinate System to add a 3 inch line that is 45 degrees from the end point of the line created above the drafter would ________.", "opta": "type @3<45 and enter", "optb": "type 3 back slash and enter", "optc": "type 3 forward slash and enter", "optd": "type 3 and try to use the Dynamic Input readout to find the end point", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A line with a tapering width can be easily created by using the ________ tool.", "opta": "circle", "optb": "eclipse", "optc": "line", "optd": "polyline", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Understanding the Cartesian coordinate system will help the beginning drafter ________.", "opta": "control the accuracy of the drawing", "optb": "produce a visible grid system", "optc": "select a different text style", "optd": "choose various line types", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The UCS icon represents the intersection of the ________.", "opta": "X axis", "optb": "Y axis", "optc": "Z axis", "optd": "All of the above", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "When using the direct entry method to create a horizontal line exactly three inches long the drafter should ________ first.", "opta": "pull the line from away from the starting point very carefully", "optb": "insure that Ortho is on", "optc": "enter 3 for the length of the line", "optd": "read the coordinate position on the Dynamic Readout", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "In order to set drawing limits for a \"C\" size architectural drawing the drafter should set the limits to ________.", "opta": "0,0 and 2,9", "optb": "0,0 and 17,11", "optc": "0,0 and 18,24", "optd": "0,0 and 34,24", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "One quick way to view the entire drawing area is to use the Zoom command by typing ________.", "opta": "type Z enter A enter", "optb": "type Z enter E enter", "optc": "type SHOWALL enter", "optd": "type ALL enter", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "When setting up a mechanical drawing in AutoCAD the drafter should set the units to ________.", "opta": "fractional", "optb": "decimal", "optc": "architectural", "optd": "metric", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "When drawing a line using the relative coordinate system a line is created from ________.", "opta": "0,0", "optb": "the ending point of the last line", "optc": "the beginning point of the last line", "optd": "none of the above", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "If you use the absolute coordinate system to create a line from a starting point of 0, 0 8 units on the X axis and 5 units on the Y axis you enter ________ for the second point.", "opta": "8,5", "optb": "5,8", "optc": "0,8", "optd": "5,0", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}]]}